<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Travels on Antoni Pawlak</title><link>https://antooni.github.io/travel/</link><description>Recent content in Travels on Antoni Pawlak</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://antooni.github.io/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>🇲🇪 Montenegro</title><link>https://antooni.github.io/travel/montenegro/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://antooni.github.io/travel/montenegro/</guid><description>Serendipity ~ the occurrence and development of events by chance in a happy or beneficial way
Montenegro and my whole experience can be very well described by this word. To be honest, before the journey, I have only known the name of the city that I am going to and that &amp;ldquo;Montenegro is beautiful&amp;rdquo;. The day before the flight I found out that a passport would be required to enter this country.</description></item><item><title>🇮🇸 Iceland</title><link>https://antooni.github.io/travel/iceland/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://antooni.github.io/travel/iceland/</guid><description>Place like no other Let&amp;rsquo;s embark together on a trip over Iceland, during which I will introduce my thoughts and memories from the Land of Ice and Fire.
I highly recommend listening to Light of the Seven in the background.
Niceland I came up with the name inside the car, when everyone was looking through the windows and constantly someone was saying &amp;ldquo;nice&amp;rdquo;. It is a nice land indeed, but only saying it is nice is an understatement.</description></item><item><title>🇳🇴 Bergen</title><link>https://antooni.github.io/travel/bergen/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://antooni.github.io/travel/bergen/</guid><description>The fjord cruise dream I wanted to have unforgettable summer trip with my girlfriend. During last year I was saving money for that, but the catch is, I did not know the destination. Until one June&amp;rsquo;s evening when I got struck by this idea: I really love nature and want to see something unique. Fjords were the first to pop out of my mind. And that was it, immediately I knew where I wanted to go.</description></item></channel></rss>