<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Developer-notes on Antoni Pawlak</title><link>https://antooni.github.io/developer-note/</link><description>Recent content in Developer-notes on Antoni Pawlak</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://antooni.github.io/developer-note/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Connect to VPN using Wireguard</title><link>https://antooni.github.io/developer-note/connect-wireguard-vpn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://antooni.github.io/developer-note/connect-wireguard-vpn/</guid><description>Connect to VPN on startup Tutorial for Linux (Ubuntu) Install Wireguard sudo apt-get wireguard Download .conf VPN configuration file from your provider Put this file inside /etc/wireguard Create a script responsible for connection and save it to your local disk sudo wg-quick up &amp;lt;name&amp;gt; where name is a name of the file inside /etc/wireguard (without .conf extension) To run this script on startup type in terminal: sudo crontab -e At the bottom of the opened file add @reboot &amp;lt;your/script/path&amp;gt; References Run file on startup as root</description></item><item><title>Connect to VPN using Wireguard</title><link>https://antooni.github.io/developer-note/encrypt-dns/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://antooni.github.io/developer-note/encrypt-dns/</guid><description>Encrypt DNS traffic Recently, I have been setting up VPN connection and during network sniffing with Wireshark I found out that all my DNS request are plain text, so there is a room to potentially see all my DNS request. What it effectively means is that a third party can observe my internet connection and see which pages I visit. To be precise, just the addresses, not the content, so it is not that much of a vulnerability, but still&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Create GitHub Page with Hugo</title><link>https://antooni.github.io/developer-note/creating-a-new-theme/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://antooni.github.io/developer-note/creating-a-new-theme/</guid><description>intro If you want to have your personal website without putting too much effort in it GitHub Pages is your way to go. You can simply push the index.html to your public folder on the main branch and you have your website. But there is a little problem, it will be a very basic one so you would have to code all the styling from scratch, not to mention logic. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry Hugo got you covered, you can install themes and setup automatic build wih github workflows, let&amp;rsquo;s see how to set it up&amp;hellip;</description></item></channel></rss>